さて　みゆきさんが余らせたナゲットを
Now, one of us is going to take the nugget
この中の誰かが頂く事になったのだが…
that Miyuki-san has left uneaten...
にらめっこで勝った人が食べることにしよう
Let's have a staring contest to decide it
まだ子供じみだ！
That's so childish!
にらめっこか　面白そうだね
Staring contest? That sounds fun
かがみが圧勝しそうだけどね
Though I think Kagamin will win for sure
何か言ったか？
Did you say something?
ではいきます
Then let's go
いらめっこしましょ　あっぷっぷ！
It's the staring contest. Blaaah!
それ　やばいって！
That's too much!
すごーい！
Amazing!
人間の顔じゃない…！
That's not something a human can do...!
ちょっと　２人ともオーバーだよ
Hey, you two are overreacting
お待たせしました　トイレが混んでまして
Thank you for waiting, the bathroom was crowded
どうしたのですか？
What happened?
ねぇ　みゆきにもさっきの顔見せてあげてよ
Hey, show that face you just made to Miyuki too
イヤだよー
I don't wanna...
みゆき　すごいんだって
Miyuki, it was so amazing
今まで見た事のない顔よ　これは
This was a face that you've never seen before in your life
じゃあ
Well then
な　何度見てもすごい！
It..it's still amazing no matter how many time I see it!
その顔は一芸入試などで役に立つかもしれませんね・・・
You could use that face for the talent part of a university application
そうだよ　こなた　それで大学受けなよ
That's right, Konata. Use that to apply for university
絶対受かるって
I'm sure you'll get accepted
あんまり嬉しくないな
That doesn't make me happy